const myQuestions = [
    {
      //Question1
      question: "How many cat breeds are there in the world?",
      answers: [
        "There are 70 breeds of cats in the world",
        "There are 100 breeds of cats in the world",
        "There are 40 breeds of cats in the world",
        "There are 90 breeds of cats in the world",
      ],
      correctAnswer:
        "There are 70 breeds of cats in the world"
    },
    {
      //Question2
      question: "How many cats are there in the world?",
      answers: [
        "There are 100-200 million cats in the world",
        "There are 400-600 million cats in the world",
        "There are 200-600 million cats in the world",
        "There are 300-700 million cats in the world",
      ],
      correctAnswer:
        "There are 200-600 million cats in the world"
    },
    {
      //Question3
      question: "The heaviest known cat weighed nearly how many pounds?",
      answers:[
       "25 Pounds",
        "35 Pounds",
        "60 Pounds",
        "50 Pounds",
      ],
      correctAnswer:
        "50 Pounds"
    },
    {
      //Question4
      question: "Where do cats rank as a popular pet in the U.S.A.",
      answers: [
        "5TH Most popular pet in the U.S.A.",
        "2ND Most popular pet in the U.S.A.",
        "1ST Most popular pet in the U.S.A.",
        "3RD Most popular pet in the U.S.A.",
      ],
      correctAnswer:
        "2ND Most popular pet in the U.S.A."
    },
    {
      //Question5
      question: "How old can cats live for?",
      answers: [
        "10-13 Years",
        "12-15 Years",
        "9-16 Years",
        "7-10 Years",
      ],
      correctAnswer:
        "12-15 Years"
    },
    {
      //Question6
      question: "The oldest known cat named Cream Puff lived for how many years?",
      answers: [
        "38 Years old",
        "15 Years old",
        "24 Years old",
        "20 Years old",
      ],
      correctAnswer:
        "38 Years old"
    },
    {
      //Question7
      question: "When was the first cat video uploaded to youtube?",
      answers: [
        "2006",
        "2007",
        "2005",
        "2004",
      ],
      correctAnswer:
         "2005"
    },
    {
      //Question8
      question: "Do cats dream like humans?",
      answers: [
        "Ture",
        "False",
      ],
      correctAnswer:
        "True"
    },
    {
      //Question9
      question: "Are the cats wiskers as wide as their body?",
      answers: [
        "True",
        "False",
      ],
      correctAnswer:
        "Ture"
    },
    {
      //Question10
      question: "How high can cats jump?",
      answers: [
        "5 Feet",
        "6 Feet",
        "9 Feet",
        "8 Feet",
      ],
      correctAnswer:
        "5 Feet"
    },
    {
      //Question11
      question: "Are all cat born with brown eyes?",
      answers: [
        "False",
        "True",
      ],
      correctAnswer:
        "False"
    }
  ];
  
  //variables to store the quiz score and question number information
  var score = 0;
  var current = 0;
  